Now we're going to construct our ears for our animal purses.
We got the panda face done, we have our cat face done, and now we're going to make the other ear for the cat.
Remember, you're going to need two pieces of your ear cut out at the same time and your piece of wire that goes in-between them.
So I have my two pieces of felt for my ear and my wire.
Place your wire towards the edge of the fabric.
It doesn't have to be right on the edge, just near the edge, and place your other piece of felt on top.
You're going to lift this up and hold it with your fingertips together.
You're going to take your needle and thread with the same color as the fabric, and you're going to go around that wire so it catches.
You're just going to stitch from the bottom up, and you're going to go around the wire so you know that it's being caught by your thread and your stitches.
Just keep continuing that, and it's just going to make little stitches all the way around.
Just make sure you're getting to the edge of the fabric and you'll know you're catching the wire.
You're going to continue this all the way around the edge of the ear.
So, I'm going to finish up sewing my ear.
Remember, just catch that wire that's inside of there.
And once you have gotten down to the edge of the ear, I don't want you to, to finish this off with a knot.
We're going to attach it right to the purse.
Okay, so notice there's a little piece of wire there.
I'm just going to bend that across so it's nice and neat.
I'm going to bring my cat over here.
I'm going to attach the ear.
I want it right there.
So then I'm going to go up from the bottom, I'm going to hold the ear in place while I attach it to the face.
And just do another running stitch right across.
You're going to go up, underneath, through the ear, attach it to the face and go back down.
Up, underneath, and go all the way across until your ear is attached.
Just like that.